of different perception towards the
arts, I think, in the UK. Like, in lots
of countries, it's like total waste of
time.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, it's got to be science or
nothing.
>> I think it's more It's more accepted in
the UK. Certainly, what we call the
humanities, so we're talking about like,
um, you know, history, English
literature, they're still seen as like
maybe not quite as impressive as STEM,
but still like They're still seen as
like serious subjects. Or you can do
so-called social sciences like economics
or, um, sociology. But they're They're
still seen as like proper subjects and
essentially because we focus on
specialization, it's kind of on you to
make the best of what you've chosen. So,
it's not like those subjects are looked
down on. It's just, "Okay, you're good
at this. See how far you can take it."
kind of thing. If you want to get a job
that's to do with the humanity, go for
it. See See what happens. But I think,
yeah, in other countries, it's much
more, "Why on earth would you want to
study that? It's a complete waste of
time." Yeah, I guess there's often
anxiety about will you be able to get a
job with that subject? Like, maybe if
you are science trained, there's more
potential jobs available for you. It's a
safer path potentially. And, you know,
we've just gone with it going through
technological revolution, so makes sense
that you maybe want to be in that home.
>> Very very good points. I think it is a
little bit sad to focus too much on on
that. I think, you know, you can't make
life all about maximizing how much money
you're going to make or how secure your
job is. You have to ultimately find some
joy in life, otherwise what's the point?
But, um,
>> Well, it's really interesting that you
say that cuz I think a lot of people
don't have that perception at all. It's
like, "Well, the most important thing is
to make enough money and have a a good
job so that you have a good social
standing."
>> [music]